What we've gone over today is sleight of hand using the Pinch Vanish and the French Drop.
Very important in magic again that I want to emphasize that you are entertaining by way of manipulating an object.
Really enjoy it, make it look effortless, make it look enjoyable to you and it will be to them as well.
You're not using magic to show them, oh look what I can do.
You really can use magic to put yourself out there to make yourself relaxed, get to know people.
It's a form of entertainment that helps people really relax.
You can really get to know somebody on a really quick and fast basis by performing an illusion.
And after all, you are pulling coins out of their ears, and so forth.
But again, enjoy.
Enjoy the reactions, enjoy your magic as much as they're going to enjoy it and you will really love the art of magic.
It's very important that that's happens as such.
But practice; don't reveal your secrets to your audience.
And never do the same trick twice, and have a good time.
That's a very important, maybe the most important rule of magic, is to enjoy it.